ILGWU. Research Department records 5780/123
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU. Research Department records
1907-1980
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/123
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Articles, reprints, pamphlets, correspondence, photographs.
This collection contains records of the National Coat and Suit Industry Board (statements of receipts and disbursements, label division reports, meetings minutes, bulletins to members, and other reports and resolutions), as well as some legal files.
5516840
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Z. Owen
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 25, 2012
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States, the ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. In 1995, the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) to form the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE).
Biographical / Historical
Formed in 1937, the Research Department of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU) supported the administrative operations of the Union and coordinated the ILGWU's investigative operations. It provided union leaders with information on wages, working conditions, economic conditions, and other matters in the women's garment industry; analyzed information for the union; and monitored developments in the industry.
In addition to providing research for union leadership, Research Department staff prepared materials for Congressional testimony, presented cases on behalf of local unions to the War Labor Board, and worked to administer the Fair Labor Standards Act. At times, the director of the Research Department represented the ILGWU in national forums.
The Department also maintained an extensive library, collecting and housing documents from Union administrative staff that were deemed substantive and of lasting value to the Union, whether produced internally or externally. The information gathered by the Department was of particular value during labor disputes and contract negotiations.
Lazare Teper was the founding director of the ILGWU's Research Department, working in that position from 1937 to 1980. Born in Russia sometime between 1906 and 1908, Teper later studied at the University of Paris and earned his doctorate at Johns Hopkins University. He died in New York City in 1985.
Scope and Contents
The Research Department records reflect the department's varied functions, documenting its role in gathering and analyzing information for international and local union leadership, representing the union before government and labor organizations, and gathering materials of research, and oftentimes historical, value. Some segments of the records focus on one aspect of the department's work, and others include documentation across the department's functions.
Research Department director Lazare Teper's papers, for example, include files relating to the Wage Stabilization Board (5780/105). The department also maintained records focused on the National Coat and Suit Industry Board (statements of receipts and disbursements, label division reports, meetings minutes, bulletins to members, and other reports and resolutions), as well as some related legal files (5780/123). Also among the documents collected by the Research Department are the New York Coat and Suit Industry Reports between 1934 and 1960. (5780/168)
Parts of the Research Department records consist primarily of collected documents from ILGWU affiliates. In this way, they resemble and, in some instances, complement the parts of the Archives Department Records (5780/121, 5780/121 PUBS), records generated by local unions (Series III), and the general collection of ILGWU publications (5780 PUBS). Research Department records of this kind contain records of predecessor unions to the ILGWU and ILGWU local union records (5780/045), or the annual report, "Conditions in the Women's Clothing Industry" (5780/078).
Other parts of the Research Department records document all of the department's functions. These records include financial and administrative reports, meeting minutes, and correspondence (5780/056, 5780/209), collected printed material (5780/168), and ILGWU statements on issues related to the garment industry (5780/209).
This collection of the Research Department primarily consists of the records of the National Coat and Suit Industry Board including statement of receipts, cessation of operations, label division reports, label sales history, by-laws, meeting minutes, committee minutes reports, reports and resolutions, bulletins sent to members, daily label sales, and miscellaneous reports.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/045: ILGWU. Research Department records 5780/056: ILGWU. Research Department collected documents 5780/078: ILGWU. Research Department reports 5780/105: ILGWU. Research Department records 5780/168: ILGWU. Research Department records 5780/209: ILGWU. Research Department records
Women's clothing industry--United States.; Labor unions--Clothing workers--United States.; Clothing workers--United States.; Industrial relations--United States.; Records.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Research Dept.
5516840
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Cessation of Operations, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1941-1959 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- National Board of the Suit and Coat Industry: Label Division Report, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- National Board of the Suit and Coat Industry: Label Division Report, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- National Board of the Suit and Coat Industry: Label Division Report, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- National Board of the Suit and Coat Industry: Label Division Report, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- National Board of the Suit and Coat Industry: Label Division Report, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- National Board of the Suit and Coat Industry: Label Division Report, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- National Board of the Suit and Coat Industry: Label Division Report, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- National Board of the Suit and Coat Industry: Label Division Report, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- National Board of the Suit and Coat Industry: Label Division Report, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- National Board of the Suit and Coat Industry: Label Sales History, 1936-1966 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Inter-office Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Inter-office Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Form Letters, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Central States Region (Siems), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Cloak Joint Board and Cloak Out-of-Town, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Eastern Region Department, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Midwest (Bialis), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- New York City Locals, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Northeast Department (Gingold), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Ohio-Kentucky, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Puerto Rico, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Southern New Jersey-Philadelphia, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Southeast, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Upper South Department, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Western States Region, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- December, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- November, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- October, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- September, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- August, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- July, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- June, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- May, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- April, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- March, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- February, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- January, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- A: General, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Americans for Democratic Action, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- COPE Political Memos, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- COPE House Marginal Congressional Districts, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- AFL-CIO COPE General [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO COPE General [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO General, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- COPE Area Conferences, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Industrial Union Department General, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- B: General, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- C: General, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Phil Kramer, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Central States Region, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Cloak Joint Board and Cloak Out-of-Town Department, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Eastern Region, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Midwest Region, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Northeast Department, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Souther New Jersey-Philadelphia, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Pacific Coast Region, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Southeast Department, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Upper South Department, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- New York City Locals, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Gore Campaign Letter, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Contributions: Alaska, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Contributions: Arizona, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Contributions: Arkansas, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Contributions: California, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Contributions: Colorado, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Contributions: Connecticut, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Contributions: Delaware, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Contributions: Florida, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Contributions: Georgia, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Contributions: Illinois, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Contributions: Indiana, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Contributions: Iowa, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Contributions: Kansas, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Contributions: Louisiana, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Contributions: Maine, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Contributions: Maryland, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Contributions: Massachusetts, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Contributions: Michigan, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Contributions: Minnesota, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Contributions: Mississippi, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Contributions: Missouri, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Contributions: Montana, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Contributions: Nevada, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Contributions: New Hampshire, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Contributions: New Jersey, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Contributions: New Mexico, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Contributions: New York, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Contributions: North Dakota, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Contributions: Ohio, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Contributions: Oklahoma, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Contributions: Oregon, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Contributions: Pennsylvania, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Contributions: South Dakota, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Contributions: Tennessee, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Contributions: Texas, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Contributions: Utah, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Contributions: Vermont, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Contributions: Virginia, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Contributions: Washington, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Contributions: West Virginia, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Contributions: Wisconsin, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Contributions: Wyoming, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Voting Records, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Undocumented Workers: Jay Mazur, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  January 21
- Tribute to Retirees, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- International Industrialization, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- U.S. Federal Security Agency: Survey of needs and problems of the members of the ILGWU prior to retirement and after retirement, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  2 copies
- Merging Funds: Louis Rolnick, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Address to the 24th Annual Meeting of the National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: David Dubinsky, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1941-1945 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1946-19650 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1951-1955 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Label Division Report, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report by Month, 1935-1941 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Division Report by Month, 1942-1953 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Sales History [folder 1 of 2], 1936-1959 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Label Sales History [folder 2 of 2], 1936-1959 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Miscellaneous Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1939-1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Miscellaneous Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1939-1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: By-laws, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: By-laws, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  July 25-26, 1935 and January 9, 1936
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  June 16-17
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  January 12-13
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  August 30-31
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  January 24-26
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  June 14-16
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  May 16-18
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  December 10-13
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  May 12-14
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  December 8-10
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  May 9-11
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  May 21-23
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  May 13-15
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  January 6-8
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  December 15-17
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  January 4-6
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  January 3-5, 1950 and January 2-4, 1951
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  January 21-23
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  January 19-21
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  January 18-20
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  January 27-29
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  February 2-4
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  February 1-3
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  May 8-10
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meeting Minutes, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  February 27-28 and March 1
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Meeting Minutes, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  February 28 and March 1-2
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Meeting Minutes, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  December 4-6
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Meeting Minutes, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recover Board: Committee Minutes Reports, 1942-1959 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Reports and Resolutions, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members, 1936-1937 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  June 1936 - January 1937
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  January 1937 - April 1937
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  April 1937 - August 1937
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  August 1937 - December 1938